<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Tutorial>
    <Titles>
        <EasyTutorial1>Die Grundlagen von SimAirport</EasyTutorial1>
        <Expansion>Große Flughafenerweiterung</Expansion>
        <Baggage>Das Gepäcksystem</Baggage>
        <FuelPA>PA-Anlage und Betanken</FuelPA>
    </Titles>
    <EndTutorial>Schließen</EndTutorial>
    <NextButton>Weiter</NextButton>
    <SkipObjective>Überspringen</SkipObjective>
    <EasyTutorial1>
        <IntroductionTitle>Willkommen bei SimAirport!</IntroductionTitle>
        <Introduction>Dies ist das erste der einfachen Tutorials.

Dieser Flughafen ist für Lernstadt das Tor zur Welt. Das kleine Terminal verfügt über die grundlegenden Einrichtungen: Transport, Tickethalle, Sicherheitskontrolle, Abflughalle, Gate und Gepäckabholung.
Das Problem: Er wurde nie fertig gebaut!</Introduction>
        <CameraMovement>Benutz die Tasten WASD, die Pfeiltasten, oder beweg den Cursor an den Bildschirmrand, um die Kamera zu verschieben. Du kannst auch die mittlere Maustaste gedrückt halten und den Cursor bewegen.

In den Optionen kannst du einstellen, wie schnell die Kamera bewegt wird.

            Dort kannst du auch die Tastenbelegung ändern.</CameraMovement>
        <TutorialWindow>Du kannst das Tutorial-Fenster verschieben, indem du die linke Maustaste gedrückt hältst und an eine neue Position ziehst.
        
Die meisten Fenster können verschoben werden. Durch Anlicken des „X“ wird das Fenster geschlossen. Dieses Fenster kann minimiert / maximiert werden um Platz zu sparen.</TutorialWindow>
        <TutorialWindowObjective>Verschiebe das Fenster!</TutorialWindowObjective>
        <UserInterface>Diese komplexe Simulation kann leicht zu verstehen sein, wenn du dich einige Momente mit der Benutzeroberfläche vertraut machst.

Du findest die allgemeinen Statistiken oben, die Einstellung der Spielgeschwindigkeit oben rechts, verschiedene Flughafenoperationen links unten und eine Auswahl von Heatmaps rechts.

Drücke die Escape-Taste, um ein beliebiges Fenster zu schließen (dies funktioniert nicht für das Tutorial-Fenster).</UserInterface>
        <ConstructIntroTitle>Die Grundlagen des Bauens</ConstructIntroTitle>
        <ConstructIntro>Eine der wichtigsten Aufgaben bei SimAirport ist das Bauen.

Objekte und Strukturen müssen von Bauarbeitern errichtet werden. Alle Innenräume müssen auf Fundamenten errichtet werden. Sobald sie fertiggestellt sind, können alle Objekte darin platziert werden.</ConstructIntro>
        <Hire4Workmen>Wenn du einen Bauauftrag erteilst werden die Baumaterialien automatisch bestellt.

Die Materialien werden mit LKWs auf der Hauptstraße in die Zone „Anlieferungen“ (im Südwesten) geliefert. Die Materialien werden dann von Bauarbeitern abgeholt und im Flughafen aufgestellt. Überschüssiges Material, z.B. aus stornierten Projekten, wird eingelagert.</Hire4Workmen>
        <Hire4WorkmenObjective>Stelle mindestens 6 Bauarbeiter ein, die im Abschnitt „Personal“ (KeyboardFunctions.StaffHub) verfügbar sind.</Hire4WorkmenObjective>
        <DragFoundation>Wähle im Menü „Bauen“ die Option „Bau“ und anschließend „Fundament“. Bist du dir nicht sicher, was ein Werkzeug oder ein Objekt tut? Du kannst den Mauszeiger darüber bewegen, um eine Beschreibung zu erhalten.
        
        Jetzt musst du warten, bis die Bauarbeiter das Fundament gebaut haben. Du kannst die Zeit mit den Steuerelementen in der oberen rechten Ecke des Bildschirms beschleunigen oder die Tasten 1/2/3 drücken, um die Geschwindigkeit festzulegen. Mit der Leertaste kannst du das Spiel anhalten.</DragFoundation>
        <DragFoundationObjective>Ziehe das Fundament über den gestreiften Bereich neben der Abflughalle. Hast du einen Fehler gemacht? Klicke mit der rechten Maustaste auf das Projekt, um den Vorgang abzubrechen.</DragFoundationObjective>
        <BuildingMistakes>Du kannst ein Bauprojekt während der Erstellung nicht nur durch Klicken mit der rechten Maustaste abbrechen, sondern Fundamente auch mit dem Einreißen-Werkzeug (KeyboardFunctions.DemolishTool) entfernen.

Wenn du versehentlich Objekte falsch platziert hast, dann verwende das Löschwerkzeug (KeyboardFunctions.ClearTool). Bist du unsicher, welches Werkzeug du verwenden sollst? Drück  KeyboardFunctions.BuildModifier, um das Entfernungswerkzeug automatisch zu erkennen.</BuildingMistakes>
        <GuestNeedsTitle>Passagierzufriedenheit und Zonen</GuestNeedsTitle>
        <GuestNeeds>Passagiere haben verschiedene Bedürfnisse wie Hunger, Blase oder Langeweile. Unser Flughafen befriedigt derzeit mit Blasenbedürfnisse mit den Toiletten.

Die Befriedigung der Bedürfnisse wird die Zufriedenheit unserer Passagiere erhöhen, wodurch sich unsere Chancen auf bessere Flugverträge verbessern.</GuestNeeds>
        <Boredom>Ein Spiele-Zone soll unseren Passagieren helfen, sich weniger gelangweilt zu fühlen. Um dies zu erreichen, müssen wir einen Bereich dafür einrichten.

Zonen sind Bereiche, in denen Passagiere und Mitarbeiter bestimmte Einrichtungen und Objekte nutzen können. Sie können die Zonenvisualisierungen mit KeyboardFunctions.ZoneToggle umschalten.</Boredom>
        <BoredomObjective>Suche den Unterpunkt "Zonen" und erstelle einen neuen Bereich mit einer Spiele-Zone.</BoredomObjective>
        <ProblemArcadeTitle>Probleme beheben</ProblemArcadeTitle>
        <ProblemArcade>Wenn mit einer Zone ein Problem besteht, wird sie rot angezeigt. Bewege den Mauszeiger darüber, um zu erfahren, welche Anforderungen nicht erfüllt sind. Meistens ist die Mindestgröße nicht erreicht oder es fehlen Objekte.

            Drücke die Taste KeyboardFunctions.RotateObject oder klicke mit der mittleren Maustaste, um ein Objekt zu drehen. Klicke mit der rechten Maustaste auf ein platziertes Objekt, um die Errichtung abzubrechen oder das Objekt zu löschen.</ProblemArcade>
        <ProblemArcadeObjective>Löse alle Probleme der Spiele-Zone, damit sie funktionsfähig ist!</ProblemArcadeObjective>
        <EnvironmentTitle>Flughafenverbesserungen und Heatmaps</EnvironmentTitle>
        <Environment>Flughäfen können für Passagiere ein unangenehmer Ort sein. Manchmal hilft eine einfache Pflanze sie aufzuheitern!

Pflanzen findest du im Bauen-Menü unter Objekte und Deko. Du kannst auch den Fussboden ändern!

In der Umweltansicht kannst du die hübschesten Bereiche deines Flughafens sehen.</Environment>
        <Decorate>Die anderen „Heatmaps“ sind ebenfalls nützlich.

Die Informationsansicht zeigt, wo Passagiere die neuesten Informationen zu ihren Flügen erhalten.

Platziere Fluginfoanzeigen und Fluginformations-Schalte, damit die Passagiere den Überblick behalten. Sonst verpassen sie möglicherweise ihre Flüge!</Decorate>
        <PlaneStandsTitle>Das fehlerhafte Gate korrigieren!</PlaneStandsTitle>
        <PlaneStands>Wir haben keine Flugzeuge! Um Flugzeuge zu bekommen, benötigen wir zunächst ein funktionierendes Gate, das mit einem Rollweg verbunden ist und einen Gate-Schalter zugewiesen hat.

Tipp: Im Bauen-Menü kannst du zum schnellen finden nach „Gate“ oder „Rollweg“ suchen. Wenn du fertig bist, klicke entweder auf den Schalter oder das Gate, um beides einander zuzuordnen.</PlaneStands>
        <PlaneStandsObjective>Bewege den Mauszeiger über das Gate, um zu sehen was das Problem ist und behebe es.</PlaneStandsObjective>
        <QueuesTitle>Warteschlangen für Gates</QueuesTitle>
        <Queues>Um die Effizienz zu verbessern, sollten alle Gate-Schalter Warteschlangen haben.

Klicke auf Bauen, dann auf Schlangen und ziehe eine neue Warteschlange aus der Nähe des Gates heraus (z.B. im rosa Bereich). Klicke dann auf den Gate-Schalter oder die Warteschlange, um beides einander zuzuordnen.

Ticketing desks and security stands can also have queues.</Queues>
        <QueuesObjective>Build and assign a queue for the gate agent desk.</QueuesObjective>
        <FlightStatusTitle>Airports Need Planes!</FlightStatusTitle>
        <FlightStatus>Now that we have a working plane stand, we need planes to attract new departing passengers, and to land arriving passengers.

On the flight status screen (KeyboardFunctions.FlightStatus), you'll see that there are currently no planes!</FlightStatus>
        <FlightManage>Open up flight management (KeyboardFunctions.FlightSchedule), where you'll see available airline contracts with daily flights. We can only support small planes in the morning, which can be filtered at the top.

In order to get PM flights, you will need to click on your runway and add lights in the upgrades menu!</FlightManage>
        <FlightManageObjective>Accept and schedule the two available flights.</FlightManageObjective>
        <RunwayLength>You can get larger planes by building larger plane stands, and by upgrading the length of your runways.

To do this, simply use the runway tool (depending on concrete or asphalt) on top of an existing runway and drag it out to extend it.</RunwayLength>
        <PlaneLands>Planes usually start arriving the next day after they have first been assigned, so you might not see any today.

It's up to you to figure out how best to balance your schedule. Too crowded, and you may make your airport chaotic and lose satisfaction. Too quiet, and the airport may not be profitable.</PlaneLands>
        <UsefulUITitle>Important Information</UsefulUITitle>
        <UsefulUI>At the top of the screen you can hover over airline interest and passenger satisfaction for details. Clicking on them gives your more options.

These two screens will help you determine how you need to improve your airport for future airlines and passengers.</UsefulUI>
        <WeatherAndUpgrades>At the top, you can also see the weather. This will affect how safe it is for planes to land.

You can click on a runway to upgrade it, and add devices to make them safer. This allows planes to land in harsher condtions.</WeatherAndUpgrades>
        <FinanceHubTitle>Becoming A Successful Tycoon</FinanceHubTitle>
        <FinanceHub>More importantly, we need to make a profit. The Finance Hub has various operations, including taking out loans, which is useful if you are low on cash.

For quickness, you can also hover over your balance at the top of the screen for a brief overview.</FinanceHub>
        <Research>Unfortunately, some operations are locked. Usually, you need either specialist staff or research. As usual, hover over a problem to see what's required.

If you are missing a staff member that you cannot hire, check the Research screen. You might need to unlock them first. Keeping up with research is important for staying competitive.</Research>
        <CommercialOperations>What's also important to your balance is your prices.
            
In the Commercial Operations screen (KeyboardFunctions.OpsControlPanel), you can adjust the prices you charge. Remember: low prices increase airline satisfaction, but high prices increases profits at the cost of satisfaction!</CommercialOperations>
        <FinaleTitle>That's the Basics</FinaleTitle>
        <Finale>That is the basics of running an airport. Feel free to expand this airport or try a new airport!
            
It is recommended that you try playing the default starter airport, or complete the other tutorials, before creating an airport from scratch.</Finale>
    </EasyTutorial1>
    <Expansion>
        <IntroductionTitle>Large Airport Expansion</IntroductionTitle>
        <Introduction>Welcome to the second easy difficulty tutorial.

Large, complex airports can be difficult for passengers to traverse. This can cause them to be late, hurting your ratings.</Introduction>
        <SolutionsTitle>Solutions To Improve Efficiency</SolutionsTitle>
        <Solutions>Solution 1: Manage your queues.

Solution 2: Build a second terminal.

Solution 3: Place moving walkways in long terminals to help passengers move faster.

Solution 4: Build on multiple floors to keep distances short.</Solutions>
        <Tip1Title>Solution 1: Managing Queues</Tip1Title>
        <Tip1>You can assign the same queue to multiple services, such as one queue to three ticketing desks. This is an optimal way of making sure all waiting passengers are served in the order they arrived.</Tip1>
        <Tip2>Sometimes a fair order is not the most efficient!

Creating a seperate queue for flight crew will allow them to bypass the main queue, which is especially useful at security. If the crew arrive late to the plane, it causes delays.</Tip2>
        <Tip3>You may also want to consider having priority queues for first class, as their satisfaction affects your airport rating much more than coach satisfaction does.

Don't skip making queues! Staff get confused about who is next to serve when everyone is crowding around, causing them to be much slower.</Tip3>
        <SecondTerminalTitle>Solution 2: Multiple Terminals</SecondTerminalTitle>
        <SecondTerminal>Multiple Terminals:

If there's enough space, and you have a large enough budget, a second terminal would be great for improving airport efficiency. This allows you to split up airplane gates between multiple security and ticketing zones, as long as they are connected!</SecondTerminal>
        <SecondTerminalProblems>This will require a lot more infrastructure to function correctly. Only do this once you are confident in how to get the first terminal working.

Tip: You could load the default map, and copy it below it to practise making one! Make sure the operational objects are assigned correctly.</SecondTerminalProblems>
        <WalwayIntroTitle>Solution 3: Moving Walkways</WalwayIntroTitle>
        <WalkwayIntro>Building walkways along very long areas of the terminal is the easiest and cheapest way to improve efficiency. This is assuming you have wide corridors to drag them down.

They can also be used by staff and baggage carts! Because each go in one-direction, consider how passengers will use them. Don't build huge ones; leave gaps so people are free to walk off them.</WalkwayIntro>
        <WalkwayTips>Just remember that long walking distances are not the only reason for passengers being late. Make sure to investigate long queues and where people are slowing down.

As explained in tutorial 1, building custom queues allows you to visually identify traffic problems.</WalkwayTips>
        <WalkwayTask>A recommended area has been shown as an example, going from security to the departure lounge. This is recommended because passengers need to get to their flights quickly.

To build them, search "Walkway" in the build menu search bar, and then simply drag in the direction you want it to be built in.</WalkwayTask>
        <WalkwayTaskObjective>Build a walkway, possibly on the recommended area.</WalkwayTaskObjective>
        <FloorsIntroTitle>Solution 4: Multiple Floors</FloorsIntroTitle>
        <FloorsIntro>Multiple Floors:
            
It might not be practical to fit in walkways if there is little corridor space.

Depending on the layout of the airport, there might be no choice but to expand upwards. This is where multiple floors come in.</FloorsIntro>
        <Controls>Use KeyboardFunctions.LevelUp to go up a floor, and KeyboardFunctions.LevelDown to go down. Or, click on the arrows to the right of the screen. This follows the American system: there is no first floor after the ground floor.

Anything you can do on the ground floor, you can do on the other floors (except terrain changes).</Controls>
        <Underground>Underground areas are useful for hiding later complicated systems, such as baggage conveyors and utilities, from passengers. You still need a foundation under where you place objects.

They can also be useful for connecting different areas, such as a terminal-island, via tunnels. You could combine a long tunnel with moving walkways!</Underground>
        <AboveGround>Higher levels can be useful for expanding your shopping areas in the departure lounge, or adding staff zones that are out of the way of passengers.

A second floor door connection is required for the larger gate sizes to connect to the terminal.</AboveGround>
        <SecondFloorOptionalTask>Feel free to build a second floor above the departure lounge, to make room for shops. Remember to connect it with stairs!

Before anything can be built on this floor, a foundation must be placed. That foundation must be placed above an existing one on the lower floor.</SecondFloorOptionalTask>
    </Expansion>
    <Baggage>
        <IntroductionTitle>Baggage Systems</IntroductionTitle>
        <Introduction>Welcome to the first advanced tutorial.
            
Baggage Systems are a must for large airports. This will allow for efficient loading and unloading of plane luggage, and swift deliveries to the Baggage Claim.</Introduction>
        <SmallAirports>Do note that if you are running a small airport, you don't need a full baggage system. To handle baggage you just need ticketing desks, a Baggage Claim zone, and extra workmen.

These workmen will drive baggage carts between the zones and gates to keep up with demand, and this will work fine for small airports.</SmallAirports>
        <SystemIntroTitle>Using Multiple Floors</SystemIntroTitle>
        <SystemIntro>Before you can start building a baggage system, you first have to get used to using multiple floors as demonstrated in the Large Airport Expansion tutorial. We'll briefly cover it here.</SystemIntro>
        <MultipleFloors>Use KeyboardFunctions.LevelUp to go up a floor, and KeyboardFunctions.LevelDown to go down. Or, click on the arrows to the right of the screen. This follows the American system: there is no first floor after the ground floor.

Anything you can do on the ground floor, you can do on the other floors (except terrain changes).</MultipleFloors>
        <UndergroundFoundation>As you can see, the underground foundation has already been built.

When you do this for your own airports, you need enough space for ramps, conveyor belts, and luggage hubs.</UndergroundFoundation>
        <ConveyorRampTitle>Step 1: Ticketing to Planes</ConveyorRampTitle>
        <ConveyorRamp>We need the luggage to get from the ticketing desks to the planes.

A conveyor ramp will deliver luggage between floors.

In the Build Menu, go to the Utilities tab for every baggage-related object (and more).</ConveyorRamp>
        <ConveyorRampObjective>Place a Conveyor Down Transition on the ground floor in the highlighted spot. If it cannot be placed, keep rotating it on that area shown and it should turn green.</ConveyorRampObjective>
        <DeskToRamp>Now we need the desks to be connected to this ramp. The direction is automatic, so it does not matter which way you drag them.
        
Note: if you wish to place things freely, place these objects where you like and skip ahead at any point. If you decide to skip, remember you'll have to figure out how to connect them yourself!</DeskToRamp>
        <DeskToRampObjective>Connect the desks to the ramp with conveyor belts on the highlighted line. You will need to wait for it to be built - remember the speed controls in the top right!</DeskToRampObjective>
        <HubTitle>Sorting The Luggage</HubTitle>
        <Hub>The luggage needs to be sorted. A baggage hub will take inputs, and sort them into outputs. You can rotate it with middle-click or by pressing KeyboardFunctions.RotateObject.

Note where the hub's entrances and exits are, based on the arrows pointing in towards it and out of it. You can right-click on any to change what type they are!</Hub>
        <HubObjective>Build a baggage hub and connect it.</HubObjective>
        <DepotTitle>Finishing Step 1: Ticketing to Planes</DepotTitle>
        <Depot>Once the luggage is sorted, it will need to be sent to a baggage depot close by to the aircraft gates. This is where they will be collected from for planes.</Depot>
        <DepotObjective>Build a baggage depot on the ground floor on the highlighted spot.</DepotObjective>
        <HubToDepot>An output from the baggage hub needs to connect to the input of the baggage depot.</HubToDepot>
        <HubToDepotObjective>Connect the depot to the hub on the highlighted squares as a guide.</HubToDepotObjective>
        <CheckDepotWorks>To check if the connections are correct, hover over the depot. It should no longer require a connection to a ticketing desk.
        
It will only deliver luggage for gates assigned to the depot. This can be taken advantage of when you have large airports with multiple depots.</CheckDepotWorks>
        <CheckDepotWorksObjective>Now click on the depot and assign it to the aircraft gate.</CheckDepotWorksObjective>
        <DepotToPlane>The baggage will not be able to get to the planes yet! Baggage cars will deliver luggage to and from depots. They are stored in hangars.

You can search for "Hangar" in the build menu or find it under structures.</DepotToPlane>
        <DepotToPlaneObjective>Build a small hangar anywhere next to a taxiway, and once constructed, add a baggage car.</DepotToPlaneObjective>
        <DepartureWorks>The baggage car will deliver luggage between the depot and the gates assigned.

That's departure flights sorted, but now we need to sort out arrivals luggage.</DepartureWorks>
        <DepotToHubTitle>Step 2: From Planes to Carousels</DepotToHubTitle>
        <DepotToHub>Firstly, let's get the arrivals luggage from the baggage depot to the hub.</DepotToHub>
        <DepotToHubObjective>Connect the conveyor belts, to match the output of the depot to the remaining input of the hub.</DepotToHubObjective>
        <Arrivals>Now passengers need a way to actually collect their luggage.

They collect these from baggage carousels, which need to be connected underground. It already comes with a ramp in the middle of it.</Arrivals>
        <ArrivalsObjective>In the Baggage Claim zone, add a carousel, which is found in Utilities.</ArrivalsObjective>
        <HubToCarousel>Finally, the luggage needs to get from the hub to the carousel!</HubToCarousel>
        <HubToCarouselObjective>Connect the remaining out of the hub to the in of the carousel.</HubToCarouselObjective>
        <FinaleTitle>Working Baggage System</FinaleTitle>
        <Finale>Congratulations, you (assuming you didn't skip) have a working baggage system!</Finale>
    </Baggage>
    <FuelPA>
        <IntroductionTitle>PA Systems and Fuel</IntroductionTitle>
        <Introduction>Welcome to the second advanced tutorial. This tutorial will help make your large airports operate better.

PA systems help stop passengers and flight crew missing their flights, while fuel services will increase the interest of airlines!</Introduction>
        <PAInfoTitle>Public Announcements</PAInfoTitle>
        <PAInfo>Firstly, let's get a PA system working. Let's not lose high ratings on confused passengers.
            
The PA system is triggered twice during the boarding process. First, when the plane begins boarding. Then, it broadcasts a "last call" about 15-20 minutes before departing.</PAInfo>
        <TechnologyTitle>Unlocking PA</TechnologyTitle>
        <Technology>You need to research Technology in order to be able to hire a CTO (Chief Technology Officer) and unlock the PA systems.

While you are waiting for it to research, you can build an office for your future CTO. During the tutorial, research is much faster than normal!</Technology>
        <TechnologyObjective>Research Technology in the research screen.</TechnologyObjective>
        <CTO>Once you have a CTO and an office, you will be able to unlock PA systems.</CTO>
        <CTOObjective>Hire a CTO and make sure that they have an office.</CTOObjective>
        <SpeakersTitle>Building the PA System</SpeakersTitle>
        <Speakers>Speakers relay announcements across the terminal. Passengers need to be close to a speaker, and in the direction of a speaker, to hear it.
        
As you are placing them, use the PA Speakers heatmap to see the area that they affect.</Speakers>
        <SpeakersObjective>Place at least 4 speakers in areas most likely to be visited by passengers. Use the PA Speakers heatmap to see coverage.</SpeakersObjective>
        <Amplifier>PA Systems use amplifiers to connect the speakers to a central electrical system.

If you have more than 4 speakers or more than 4 gates, build a HD amplifier to handle the additional load.</Amplifier>
        <AmplifierObjective>Drag an electrical zone room, and place an amplifier inside. Make sure it meets the requirements.</AmplifierObjective>
        <Connect>You'll need to connect each speaker to the amplifier, by clicking on the amplifier, and selecting Connect To.

At the moment, your PA system will be broadcasting nothing! You can assign up to four gates that you want it to broadcast information about, by clicking on the amplifier and assigning each one.</Connect>
        <CompletedPATitle>Fueling Services</CompletedPATitle>
        <CompletedPA>Your PA system should now be working!

Next, we'll look at fueling services.

Refueling planes helps your airport earn extra income, improve airline satisfaction ratings, and potentially get access to new contracts.</CompletedPA>
        <FuelDepotTitle>Getting The Fuel</FuelDepotTitle>
        <FuelDepot>Fuel is delivered once per day, to a depot where delivery trucks will deliver new fuel from outside of the airport.</FuelDepot>
        <FuelDepotObjective>Build a fuel depot by the main road.</FuelDepotObjective>
        <FuelTanks>Fuel is stored in fuel tanks. Large fuel tanks are available, but are very expensive. They need to be connected to the depot, and you can save on piping by building them close.

You can see which pipes have fuel if they are red (empty) or green (full/connected to depot).</FuelTanks>
        <FuelTanksObjective>Build at least two regular fuel tanks and connect them to the depot.</FuelTanksObjective>
        <RefuelingStationTitle>From Storage to Planes</RefuelingStationTitle>
        <RefuelingStation>Trucks will drive along the taxiway to a refuel station to fill up.</RefuelingStation>
        <RefuelingStationObjective>Build a refuel station next to the taxiway, and connect it to the rest of the fuel network with pipes.</RefuelingStationObjective>
        <Transport>It's time to buy the trucks that will do the work. You'll need to build a hangar first, and buy the truck from the hangar's menu.</Transport>
        <TransportObjective>Buy at least one fuel truck.</TransportObjective>
        <BuyFuelTitle>The Business of Fuel</BuyFuelTitle>
        <BuyFuel>Go to Operations, and click Fuel Services. You can buy fuel and sell it. If you keep an eye on the market price and are shrewd enough, you can make a profit dealing fuel!</BuyFuel>
        <BuyFuelObjective>Buy at least 10000 fuel. You can purchase this once, or set it to auto-purchase every day.</BuyFuelObjective>
        <Active>If you find that the status of fuel services is "Not Active", try hovering over it to see what problems there are.

You will need to set a price scheme. Try each one; there is information below each one to help you choose which pricing method is better.</Active>
        <MoreInfo>Make sure to scroll down the fuel services window to see more information.

In future, you may want to upgrade your aircraft gates to have fuel ports, which will more efficiently delivery fuel to your planes.</MoreInfo>
        <FinaleTitle>Working Systems!</FinaleTitle>
        <Finale>You now have working PA and fuel systems!</Finale>
    </FuelPA>
</Tutorial>
