<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<Tutorial>
    <Titles>
        <EasyTutorial1>SimAirport 基础知识</EasyTutorial1>
        <Expansion>大型机场建设</Expansion>
        <Baggage>行李系统</Baggage>
        <FuelPA>广播系统和燃油供应</FuelPA>
        <Scheduling>员工调度</Scheduling>
        <FoodStores>食品和商店</FoodStores>
        <NeedsNegotiate>航空公司需求和谈判</NeedsNegotiate>
    </Titles>
    <EndTutorial>关闭</EndTutorial>
    <NextButton>下一步</NextButton>
    <SkipObjective>跳过</SkipObjective>
    <EasyTutorial1>
        <IntroductionTitle>欢迎来到 SimAirport!</IntroductionTitle>
        <Introduction>这是本教程的第一步。在整个过程中，通过单击蓝色的信息图标和箭头来获取有用的图像说明。
            这个机场是莱茵维尔通往世界的门户。它的小型候机楼有基本设施：交通、票务、安检、候机厅、一个（坏掉的）登机门和行李区。
            问题是他们一直没有建造完毕！</Introduction>
        <CameraMovement>使用W、A、S、D、方向键或将光标移动到屏幕边缘以滚动屏幕。您也可以按住鼠标中键并移动光标以拖动屏幕。
            在显示设置中，可以调整移动相机的速度。您还可以在设置中自定义快捷键。</CameraMovement>
        <TutorialWindow>您可以在教程窗口按住鼠标左键，将其拖动到新位置。
            大多数窗口都可以拖动，并通过 x 按钮关闭。如果您需要此窗口占用较少的空间，可以将其最小化/最大化。</TutorialWindow>
        <TutorialWindowObjective>拖动窗口！</TutorialWindowObjective>
        <UserInterface>如果您花一些时间观察用户界面，那么这个看起来复杂的系统就很容易理解。
            你在顶部可以看到一般的统计数据，在右上角有时间控制，在左下角有各种机场操作，在右下角有信息热图选择。
            按Esc键关闭任何顶部窗口（这在教程窗口中不起作用）。</UserInterface>
        <ConstructIntroTitle>基础建设</ConstructIntroTitle>
        <ConstructIntro>对于Simairport来说，最重要的事情之一是建设。
            设备和结构只能由工人建造。所有室内房间必须建在地基上，一旦完工，任何室内物品都可以放在里面。</ConstructIntro>
        <Hire4Workmen>指定建筑区域时，建筑材料将自动采购。
            材料由卡车沿着主干道运送到运输区（西南）。然后由工人收集材料，放置在机场周围（储存区）。
            所有的备用材料（如来自取消项目的材料），都将被运送到储存区。</Hire4Workmen>
        <Hire4WorkmenObjective>在员工管理中心至少雇佣（总共）6 名建筑工人。快捷键(KeyboardFunctions.StaffHub)</Hire4WorkmenObjective>
       <DragFoundation>在“建造”菜单中选择“建筑物”，然后选择“地基”。不确定需要哪种物品？
           您可以将鼠标悬停在上面查看物品描述信息。您需要等待工人建造它，如果等不及，您可以使用屏幕右上角的加速功能加快时间，
           或者按1/2/3键来控制时间速度，用空格键暂停/继续时间。</DragFoundation>
        <DragFoundationObjective>拖拽地基，以覆盖候机厅的区域范围。修错地方了？在工人开始之前，左键单击要取消的项目。</DragFoundationObjective>
        <BuildingMistakes>您不仅可以通过左键单击取消施工期间的项目，还可以使用“拆除”快捷键 (KeyboardFunctions.DemolishTool)取消地基。
            或者，如果您不小心放错了一些对象，请使用清除工具 (KeyboardFunctions.ClearTool).。
            不确定要使用哪种工具？按 KeyboardFunctions.BuildModifier 自动检测删除工具。
            您也可以在左键单击菜单中增加或减少项目的工作人员优先级！</BuildingMistakes>
        <GuestNeedsTitle>乘客需求和分区</GuestNeedsTitle>
        <GuestNeeds>乘客有各种各样的需求，如饥饿、厕所和无聊。我们的机场发现很多乘客需要厕所以满足生理需求。
            处理这些问题将提高乘客的满意度，这将提高我们获得更好航空合同的机会。</GuestNeeds>
        <Boredom>街机游戏区应该能让我们的乘客摆脱无聊。要做到这一点，我们需要为它划分一个区域。
            区域是指定乘客和工作人员可以使用某些设施和物品的区域。您可以使用 KeyboardFunctions.ZoneToggle 切换区域是否可见.</Boredom>
        <BoredomObjective>找到“区域”面板，为街机游戏区划分新区域。可以只建造一个满足基础功能的区域，或完全布置一个完整的街机区。</BoredomObjective>
        <ProblemArcadeTitle>如何解决问题</ProblemArcadeTitle>
        <ProblemArcade>如果房间出现问题，它就会变红。把鼠标悬停在它上面看看它需要什么。大多数问题要么是大小不对，要么是缺少必要设施。
            按 KeyboardFunctions.RotateObject 或鼠标中键单击以旋转对象。右键单击放置的对象以取消或删除它。</ProblemArcade>
        <ProblemArcadeObjective>修复街机区的问题，直到它具备应有功能！</ProblemArcadeObjective>
        <EnvironmentTitle>完善机场与需求信息图</EnvironmentTitle>
        <Environment>机场可能会让乘客感到沮丧。有时一株简陋的植物就能让他们振作起来！
            布景可以在“建筑”菜单的“对象和装饰”下找到。您也可以更改地板设计！
            您可以使用环境热图查看机场最吸引人的区域。</Environment>
        <Decorate>其他的热图也很有用。
            信息覆盖热图显示乘客可以在哪里获得航班的最新信息。
            放置信息显示器和信息亭，帮助乘客跟踪，否则他们可能会错过航班。</Decorate>
        <PlaneStandsTitle>修复坏掉的停机坪！</PlaneStandsTitle>
        <PlaneStands>我们没有飞机！为了得到飞机，我们首先需要一个正常工作的停机位，连接到一个滑行道，并分配一个登机口服务台。
            示：在“建筑”菜单中，您可以搜索“门”（Gate）或“滑行道”（Taxiway）以快速找到它们。
            一旦建成，点击登机门或登机口服务台的任意一个，将它们分配给彼此。</PlaneStands>
        <PlaneStandsObjective>将鼠标悬停在登机门上，查看错误或丢失的内容，然后解决问题。</PlaneStandsObjective>
        <QueuesTitle>如何设置排队</QueuesTitle>
        <Queues>为了提高效率，所有的登机台都应该排好队。
            单击“建筑”，然后单击“队列”，然后从靠近门的位置拖出一个新队列（请参见粉色区域示例）。然后，单击登机口服务台或队列将它们彼此分配。
            售票处和安检区也可以排队。</Queues>
        <QueuesObjective>为登机口服务台建立并分配一个队列。</QueuesObjective>
        <FlightStatusTitle>机场需要飞机！</FlightStatusTitle>
        <FlightStatus>现在，既然我们有了一个正常工作的停机位，我们就需要飞机来吸引新的离港旅客，并迎接到港旅客。
            在航班管理菜单 (KeyboardFunctions.FlightStatus), 你将看到，目前我们还没有飞机！</FlightStatus>
        <FlightManage>打开航班管理 (KeyboardFunctions.FlightSchedule), 在那里你可以看到每日航班的可用合同。
            我们目前只能在白天支持小型飞机，可以在顶部过滤。为了获得夜间航班，您需要点击您的跑道，并在升级菜单中添加跑道灯！</FlightManage>
        <FlightManageObjective>接受并安排两个可用的航班。</FlightManageObjective>
        <RunwayLength>你可以通过建造更大的飞机停机位和升级跑道长度来获得更大的飞机合同。因为小型飞机可以使用小型跑道，所以你不需要在早期就这么做。
            准备好后，只需在现有跑道顶部使用跑道工具（取决于混凝土或沥青），然后将其拖出以延长跑道。</RunwayLength>
        <PlaneLands>飞机通常在第一次被分配后的第二天开始到达，所以你今天可能看不到任何东西。
            由您决定怎样平衡合理的安排航班日程。太拥挤，你可能会使机场陷入混乱，降低乘客满意度。太清闲，机场可能不会盈利。</PlaneLands>
        <UsefulUITitle>重要信息</UsefulUITitle>
        <UsefulUI>
            同样在屏幕顶部，您可以将鼠标悬停在航空公司的兴趣和乘客满意度上，以了解详细信息。单击它们可以提供更多选项。
            这两个屏幕将帮助您确定未来如何对机场进行改造，以满足航空公司和乘客。</UsefulUI>
        <WeatherAndUpgrades>在屏幕顶部，你还可以看到天气状况。这将影响飞机着陆的安全性。
            你可以点击跑道进行升级，并添加升级设备使其更安全。这使得飞机可以在更恶劣的条件下着陆。</WeatherAndUpgrades>
        <FinanceHubTitle>变成真正的大亨</FinanceHubTitle>
        <FinanceHub>最重要的是，我们需要盈利。金融中心有各种各样的业务，包括贷款，如果你现金不足，这能帮上你。
            为了方便，您还可以将鼠标悬停在屏幕顶部的余额上，以获得简短的概述。</FinanceHub>
        <Research>不幸的是，一些操作是锁定状态。通常，你需要专家或研究人员。像往常一样，将鼠标悬停在一个问题上以查看需要什么。
            如果你找不到或不能雇佣要求的员工，请查看研究屏幕。您可能需要先解锁它们。跟上研究进度对于保持竞争力很重要。</Research>
        <CommercialOperations>机场的服务定价对你的余额来说同样重要。在“商业运营”屏幕 (KeyboardFunctions.OpsControlPanel), 
            您可以调整收费。记住：低价会提高航空公司的满意度，但高价会以满意度为代价增加利润！</CommercialOperations>
        <FinaleTitle>这是经营机场的基础知识</FinaleTitle>
        <Finale>这是运营机场的基础。请随意扩大这个机场或尝试修建一个新机场！
            建议您初次创建机场时，从系统默认机场开始，或完成其他教程。</Finale>
    </EasyTutorial1>
    <Expansion>
        <IntroductionTitle>大型机场建设</IntroductionTitle>
        <Introduction>欢迎学习第二个基础教程。大型、复杂的机场可能很难让乘客通过。这会导致他们迟到，使您的收益受损。</Introduction>
        <SolutionsTitle>提高效率的解决方案</SolutionsTitle>
        <Solutions>提高效率的解决方案 
            解决方案1：管理队列。
            解决方案2：建立第二个登机口。
            解决方案3：将自动扶梯放置在较远的登机口，以帮助乘客更快地移动。
            解决方案4：建在多个楼层上，以保证登机距离最短。</Solutions>
        <Tip1Title>解决方案1：管理队列</Tip1Title>
        <Tip1>您可以将同一队列分配给多个服务窗口，例如一个队列分配给三个票务台。
            这是确保所有候机乘客按照他们到达的顺序得到服务的最佳方式。</Tip1>
        <Tip2>有时公平不等于效率！
            为机组人员创建单独的队列将允许他们绕过主队列，这在安全方面特别有用。如果机组人员晚到飞机上，会造成航班延误。</Tip2>
        <Tip3>您可能还需要考虑为头等舱安排优先队列，因为他们的满意度对您的机场评分的影响远大于长途汽车满意度。
            不要忽视排队！当每个人都挤在一起时，工作人员会对下一个服务对象感到困惑，从而使他们慢得多。</Tip3>
        <SecondTerminalTitle>解决方案2：多个登机点</SecondTerminalTitle>
        <SecondTerminal>多个登机点：如果有足够的空间，并且你有足够大的预算，第二个航站楼将是提高机场效率的好办法。
            这允许您为不同航站楼修建各自独立的售票区、安检区，与登机口，只要把它们各自连接好！
            （This allows you to split up airplane gates between multiple security and ticketing zones, 
            as long as they are connected!）</SecondTerminal>
        <SecondTerminalProblems>这将需要更多的基础设施才能正常工作。只有当您有信心完成一个正常运作的航站楼时，才能这样做。
            提示：您可以复制映射区，并将其复制到它下面以练习生成映射！确保正确分配操作对象。</SecondTerminalProblems>
        <WalwayIntroTitle>解决方案3：自动扶梯</WalwayIntroTitle>
        <WalkwayIntro>为航站楼内较远的区域修建自动扶梯是提高效率的最简单和最便宜的方法。这是假设你有宽阔的走廊把它们拖下来。
            他们也可以被工作人员和行李车使用！因为每个人都朝一个方向走，所以要考虑乘客将如何使用它们。
            不要把扶梯修的太长，留些空隙，以便乘客们可以在需要时自由地离开。</WalkwayIntro>
        <WalkwayTips>记住，长途步行并不是乘客迟到的唯一原因。一定要调查长队和人们减速的地方。
            如教程1所述，设置好乘客排队方式以方便您直观地发现流量问题出现在哪里。</WalkwayTips>
        <WalkwayTask>推荐使用的区域包括，从安检区到候机厅。建议这样做是因为乘客需要快速到达他们的航班。
            要创建它们，请在“建筑”菜单搜索栏中搜索“通道”（Walkway），然后简单地沿要修建通道的方向拖动。</WalkwayTask>
        <WalkwayTaskObjective>在推荐区域修建一条自动扶梯。</WalkwayTaskObjective>
        <FloorsIntroTitle>解决方案4：多层</FloorsIntroTitle>
        <FloorsIntro>多层：
            如果走廊空间很小，那么在走道上安装可能不太现实。
            根据机场的布局，可能别无选择，只能向上扩展。这时只能引入多层建筑。</FloorsIntro>
        <Controls>使用 KeyboardFunctions.LevelUp 到达上一层,  KeyboardFunctions.LevelDown 去下一层。
            或者，单击屏幕右侧的箭头。这里遵循美国的制度：地基楼层算0层，整个建筑标识中没有一楼。
            你在一楼做的任何事情在其他楼层都可以做（地形变化除外）。</Controls>
        <Underground>地下区域有助于向乘客隐藏后期复杂的系统，有些设备你需要放在地下楼层，如行李传送带和公用设施。
            它们还可用于通过隧道连接不同区域，如终端岛（terminal-island）。你可以把一条长隧道和自动扶梯结合起来！</Underground>
        <AboveGround>扩展您在候机厅的购物区，或者增加不妨碍乘客的工作人员区域，对提高乘客满意度非常有用。
            大尺寸的登机门需要通过二楼才能连接到登机口。</AboveGround>
        <SecondFloorOptionalTask>您可以在候机厅上方建造一个二楼，为商店腾出空间。记得用楼梯把它们连接起来！
            在地板上任何东西都可以建造之前，必须放置一个地基。这个地基只能放在下层楼层之上。</SecondFloorOptionalTask>
    </Expansion>
    <Baggage>
        <IntroductionTitle>行李系统</IntroductionTitle>
        <Introduction>欢迎使用第一个高级教程。
            大型机场必须配备行李系统。这将有助于有效地装卸飞机行李，并迅速地将货物交给行李领取处。</Introduction>
        <SmallAirports>请注意，如果您经营的是一个小型机场，您不需要一个完整的行李系统。要处理行李，您只需要售票台、行李领取区和额外的工人。
            这些工人将在区域和登机门之间驾驶行李车，以满足需求，对于小型机场来说，这比行李系统划算。</SmallAirports>
        <SystemIntroTitle>使用多层</SystemIntroTitle>
        <SystemIntro>在开始修建行李系统之前，首先必须习惯于使用大型机场扩建教程中演示的多层。我们在这里简单介绍一下。</SystemIntro>
        <MultipleFloors>使用 KeyboardFunctions.LevelUp 到达上一层,  KeyboardFunctions.LevelDown 去下一层。或者，单击屏幕右侧的箭头。
            这里遵循美国的制度：地基楼层算0层，整个建筑标识中没有一楼。
            你在一楼做的任何事情在其他楼层都可以做（地形变化除外）。</MultipleFloors>
        <UndergroundFoundation>正如你所看到的，地下楼层已建成。
            当你为自己的机场这样做时，你需要足够的空间来放置坡道、传送带和行李中转站。</UndergroundFoundation>
        <ConveyorRampTitle>第一步：检票</ConveyorRampTitle>
        <ConveyorRamp>我们需要从售票处拿到飞机的行李。一个传送带坡道将在楼层之间运送行李。
            在建筑菜单中，转到公共事业选项卡，找到与行李系统相关的设备。</ConveyorRamp>
        <ConveyorRampObjective>在一楼突出显示的位置放置一个输送机向下过渡段。
            如果无法放置，请在显示的区域继续旋转，直到它变为绿色。</ConveyorRampObjective>
        <DeskToRamp>现在我们需要把检票台与坡道连接好。传送带方向是自动的，所以从那个方向拖动传送带并不重要。
            注意：如果你想自由地放置物品，可以跳过此段教程，并把这些物品放在你喜欢的地方。
            如果您决定跳过，请记住，您必须自己解决如何连接它们！</DeskToRamp>
        <DeskToRampObjective>在突出显示的线路上建造传送带，并将售票台连接到坡道上。您需要等待工人完成建造-可以使用右上角的速度控制！</DeskToRampObjective>
        <HubTitle>整理行李</HubTitle>
        <Hub>行李需要分类。行李中心将接收输入，并将其分类为输出。您可以通过单击鼠标中键或按 KeyboardFunctions.RotateObject.来旋转它。
            注意枢纽的入口和出口在哪里，根据“指向它”和“它指向”的箭头。您可以右键单击任意更改它们的类型！</Hub>
        <HubObjective>建立一个行李中心并连接它。</HubObjective>
        <DepotTitle>完成步骤1：飞机票务</DepotTitle>
        <Depot>一旦行李分拣完毕，就需要将其送到离登机口较近的行李站。他们在这里为乘客行李做分拣。</Depot>
        <DepotObjective>在一楼突出显示的地方建立一个行李仓库。</DepotObjective>
        <HubToDepot>行李中心的输出需要连接到行李库的输入。</HubToDepot>
        <HubToDepotObjective>以高亮区为提示，连接行李库。</HubToDepotObjective>
        <CheckDepotWorks>要检查连接是否正确，请将鼠标悬停在行李库上方。它不需要再连接到售票处。
            它只为分配到车辆段的登机门运送行李。当你有多个站点的大型机场时，可以利用这一点。</CheckDepotWorks>
        <CheckDepotWorksObjective>现在单击仓库并将其分配到飞机登机口。</CheckDepotWorksObjective>
        <DepotToPlane>行李还不能上飞机！行李车将把行李送到机库或从机库运出。它们存放在机库里。
            您可以在建筑菜单中搜索“机库”（ Hangar），或者在结构下找到它。
            （这里说的机库其实是机场工程车的车库，行李车，燃油车都停在这里，不知道为什么叫机库，可能是有后续开发安排）</DepotToPlane>
        <DepotToPlaneObjective>在靠近滑行道的任何地方建造一个小机库（车库），一旦建造完成，就添加一辆行李车。</DepotToPlaneObjective>
        <DepartureWorks>行李车将在车辆段和指定的登机门之间运送行李。
            这是出发航班的分类，但现在我们需要分类到港行李。</DepartureWorks>
        <DepotToHubTitle>第二步：从飞机到传送带</DepotToHubTitle>
        <DepotToHub>首先，让我们把到达的行李从行李站拿到中转站。</DepotToHub>
        <DepotToHubObjective>连接传送带，使车辆段的输出与行李中心的其余输入相匹配。</DepotToHubObjective>
        <Arrivals>现在，乘客需要一种方法来实际领取行李。
            他们从行李传送带收集行李，传送带需要连接到地下。它中间已经有一个斜坡了。</Arrivals>
        <ArrivalsObjective>在行李领取区，添加一个转盘，在公共事业中找到。</ArrivalsObjective>
        <HubToCarousel>最后，行李需要从中心到传送带！</HubToCarousel>
        <HubToCarouselObjective>将行李中心的其余部分连接到传送带的输入端。</HubToCarouselObjective>
        <FinaleTitle>行李系统开始工作</FinaleTitle>
        <Finale>祝贺你，你（假设你没有跳过）有一个有效的行李系统！</Finale>
    </Baggage>
    <FuelPA>
        <IntroductionTitle>广播系统与燃油供应</IntroductionTitle>
        <Introduction>欢迎使用第二个高级教程。本教程将帮助您的大型机场更好地运营。
            PA系统（广播系统）有助于防止乘客和机组人员错过航班，而燃油服务将增加航空公司的兴趣！</Introduction>
        <PAInfoTitle>公告</PAInfoTitle>
        <PAInfo>首先，让我们让一个PA系统工作。不要让乘客因为困惑给我们差评。
            PA系统在登机过程中触发两次。首先，当飞机开始登机时会进行一次广播。然后，它会在出发前15-20分钟播放“最后一次通知”。</PAInfo>
        <TechnologyTitle>解锁广播系统</TechnologyTitle>
        <Technology>你需要研究技术，以便能够雇用一名首席技术官（CTO）并解锁PA系统。
            当你在等待它的研究时，你可以为你未来的首席技术官建立一个办公室。在教程中，研究比正常情况下要快得多！</Technology>
        <TechnologyObjective>在科研窗口选择要研究的技术。</TechnologyObjective>
        <CTO>一旦你有了一个CTO和一个办公室，你就可以打开PA系统了。</CTO>
        <CTOObjective>雇佣一名首席技术官，确保他们有一个办公室。</CTOObjective>
        <SpeakersTitle>建立PA系统</SpeakersTitle>
        <Speakers>扬声器通过终端传递公告。乘客需要靠近扬声器，并朝扬声器的方向听。
            放置时，使用PA扬声器热图查看其影响的区域。</Speakers>
        <SpeakersObjective>在乘客最可能访问的区域至少放置4个扬声器。使用PA扬声器热图查看覆盖范围。</SpeakersObjective>
        <Amplifier>PA系统使用放大器将扬声器连接到中央电气系统。
            如果你有4个以上的扬声器或4个以上的门，建立一个高清放大器来处理额外的负载。</Amplifier>
        <AmplifierObjective>创建一个电气区域室，并在其中放置一个放大器。确保符合要求。</AmplifierObjective>
        <Connect>您需要通过单击放大器并选择连接到，将每个扬声器连接到放大器。
            目前，您的PA系统将不会广播任何内容！通过点击放大器并分配每个登机门，您可以分配多达四个您想要它广播信息的登机门。</Connect>
        <CompletedPATitle>燃油系统</CompletedPATitle>
        <CompletedPA>Your PA系统现在应该可以工作了！接下来，我们来看看加油服务。
            给飞机加油有助于机场赚取额外收入，提高航空公司的满意度，并有可能获得新合同。</CompletedPA>
        <FuelDepotTitle>获取燃料</FuelDepotTitle>
        <FuelDepot>燃料每天往燃油库运送一次，在那里运送卡车将从机场外运送新的燃料。</FuelDepot>
        <FuelDepotObjective>在主干道旁建一个燃料库。</FuelDepotObjective>
        <FuelTanks>燃油储存在油箱中。有大油箱，但很贵。它们需要连接到仓库，您可以通过关闭它们来节省管道费用。
            您可以看到哪些管道有燃油，红色（空的）或绿色（满的/连接到仓库）。</FuelTanks>
        <FuelTanksObjective>至少建造两个常规油箱，并将它们连接到仓库。</FuelTanksObjective>
        <RefuelingStationTitle>从仓库到飞机</RefuelingStationTitle>
        <RefuelingStation>卡车将沿着滑行道开到加油站加油。</RefuelingStation>
        <RefuelingStationObjective>在滑行道旁建一个加油站，并用管道将其连接到燃油网络的其余部分。</RefuelingStationObjective>
        <Transport>是时候买辆车了。你需要先建一个机库（车库），然后从机库（车库）菜单上买卡车。</Transport>
        <TransportObjective>至少买一辆加油车。</TransportObjective>
        <BuyFuelTitle>燃料生意</BuyFuelTitle>
        <BuyFuel>转到“操作”，然后单击“燃油服务”。你可以买燃料卖。如果你关注市场价格，并且足够精明，你就可以赚一笔交易燃料的利润！</BuyFuel>
        <BuyFuelObjective>购买至少10000个燃料。您可以购买一次，也可以将其设置为每天自动购买。</BuyFuelObjective>
        <Active>如果您发现燃油服务的状态为“未激活”，请尝试将鼠标悬停在其上方，以查看存在哪些问题。
            你需要制定一个价格方案。每种方法都可以尝试一下，下面有一些信息可以帮助您选择哪种定价方法更好。</Active>
        <MoreInfo>向下滚动Fuel Services（燃油服务）窗口以查看更多信息。
            在未来，你可能会想升级你的飞机的登机门，以拥有燃料港口，这将更有效地向你的飞机输送燃料。</MoreInfo>
        <FinaleTitle>系统正常运行！</FinaleTitle>
        <Finale>你现在有工作的PA和燃油系统！</Finale>
    </FuelPA>
    <Scheduling>
        <IntroductionTitle>调度工人教程</IntroductionTitle>
        <Introduction>欢迎使用“调度人员”教程！
            在这里，您将学习如何为对象和区域分配计划的操作时间。
            这很有用，因为它可以让您在清闲的时候节省工人的成本，或者在繁忙的时候增加工人的数量。</Introduction>
        <HowItWorks>整个机场每天都有一个时间表（我们稍后再讨论）。它被分成多个班次，每个班次可以有不同的设置。
            这些设置允许您更改管理每个区域或对象的工作人员数量。如右图所示，你可以让一半的保安在清闲的时候下班。
            这可以设置在凌晨2点到4点之间，随后在凌晨4点到8点之间进行轮班，两个警卫都在。</HowItWorks>
        <StaffHubTitle>谁可以被安排？</StaffHubTitle>
        <StaffHub>In the Staff Hub screen, you can hover over each type of worker to find out which ones can be scheduled. For example, security is shown to allow schedules, therefore, objects that are ran by security can be scheduled to be open at certain times of the day.
        
Notice how each one has a management overhead fee. This is increased for each scheduled staff per day to cover the costs to manage schedules.</StaffHub>
        <SchedulerTitle>The Staff Deployment Screen</SchedulerTitle>
        <Scheduler>Here you can see the staff deployment screen. Throughout the airport, there should be numbers showing the number of staff assigned to each object that allows scheduling.
        
At the bottom of the screen is a timeline, showing the shift changes. At the moment there should be just one shift created. This means that whatever settings are created for this shift will be applied for the entirety of the day.</Scheduler>
        <Timeline>On here you can add schedules, and for each schedule you can change the number of staff at each post.</Timeline>
        <TimelineObjective>Create a new schedule by clicking on the plus button. After it is named you will be able to assign it.</TimelineObjective>
        <AssigningTimes>Make sure it is selected (at the top of the timeline it says which is currently selected), then click a start time and drag across. It snaps to the nearest 30 minutes.

An example would be creating a night schedule from midnight - 4am and dragging again at 10pm - midnight.</AssigningTimes>
        <RemoveRename>You can remove or rename a schedule by clicking on one of the options next to the schedule editor title.
        
The last option is to copy the times from another schedule, which is useful if you only need to make small adjustments to an existing one.

It has just two steps! Step 1: click on the schedule you wish to receive the changes. Step 2: select copy from, and select the schedule.</RemoveRename>
        <AddRemoveStaff>With schedules setup, you can continue to adjust the number of workers at each object. For example, in a day shift you could have 1 staff at a ticketing desk, and in a night shift have 0.
        
Most can only have a maximum of 1 staff (hover over each object to see the limits). Some objects, such as the kiosks and kitchens, can have multiple staff to make them more efficient.</AddRemoveStaff>
        <SeeIt>To see the schedules in action, let time pass and watch them arrive and leave at the various times.
        
You will need a drop off and pickup zone for this to happen, because workers arrive and leave via transport. The more schedules you add, the more you can fine tune the coordination of your workers.

You can see how many staff are on the next bus in the Staff Hub.</SeeIt>
        <EndTitle>Tutorial Completed</EndTitle>
        <End>You can now schedule when objects will be ran by staff, and get finer control over your airport.</End>
        <HowItWorksTitle>How It Works</HowItWorksTitle>
        <StaffTypes>Remember that there are different types of workers. To make managing their schedules easier, each type has their own timeline.</StaffTypes>
        <StaffTypesObjective>Use the dropdown to change the type of worker.</StaffTypesObjective>
    </Scheduling>
    <FoodStores>
        <IntroductionTitle>Food and Shopping Tutorial</IntroductionTitle>
        <Introduction>Welcome to the food and shopping tutorial! This will cover how to build cafes, kitchens, and stores; and how pax choose where to eat and shop.

This can be profitable for your airport while making passengers happier.</Introduction>
        <FoodTitle>Food and Drinks</FoodTitle>
        <Food>Pax will get hungry, and there are various types of food to help this.
        
First there are food vending machines, which offer the least satisfaction, and can even make your passengers a little frustrated! These are only suitable for small airports; however, a basic food offering is better than no food at all!</Food>
        <Drinks>Pax can also get thirsty, and drink vending machines have the same effect on passengers with thirst that food vending machines have on hunger!</Drinks>
        <KiosksCafes>Kiosks and cafes offer much better food and drinks. These have a much higher effect on hunger and thirst, and do not frustrate your pax.

There are different types of higher quality foods and drinks available. Each passenger arrives with a preferred food and drink, and will only eat or drink that type. If that is not available, they will seek a vending machine instead!</KiosksCafes>
        <FoodTypes>Each kiosk specializes in a food or drink type, and you can hover over their build menu options to find out! Only people who like pizza will go to the pizza kiosk, for example. The bar sells multiple types of drinks.

The cafe is unique as it sells the food types based on what displays and dispensers you add to it. While it is true that the cafe can serve every food and drink type in much less floor space than the kiosks, this can also make it extremely busy.</FoodTypes>
        <BuildingTitle>Building Kiosks and Cafes</BuildingTitle>
        <Building>To build a kiosk works the same as any other object. Once built, you will need to assign it to a kitchen, which also works the same as any other assignment in-game by clicking on it, clicking Assign To, and then selecting the kitchen zone.</Building>
        <BuildingObjective>Zone a kitchen and get it functioning.
Build a pizza joint in the terminal and assign it to the kitchen zone.</BuildingObjective>
        <CafeRequirements>Cafes require a Cafe zone to be created first, then you can hover over it to see the requirements.

The food displays and drink dispensers are where pax collect their unpaid food and drinks, then they take them to a cash register to pay for them. They cannot eat or drink until they have paid for them! Tables and chairs can be placed, where only passengers who bought items from that zone can sit down at them.</CafeRequirements>
        <Kitchens1Title>Food and Drinks Preparation</Kitchens1Title>
        <Kitchens1>Your drink despensers and drink kiosks (the coffee kiosk and bars) need to be restocked by workmen. Deliveries of them will arrive in supply boxes at delivery zones, at a default time of midnight. You can adjust this in the Deliveries screen inside the Operations controller.

Kitchen zones are required to cook food for kiosks and displays in the cafes.</Kitchens1>
        <Kitchens2>This kitchen is not ready to start taking orders! To see what is needed, click on the kitchen and select Kitchen Overview. This brings up the overview screen, that allows you to see what steps are needed for each food type.</Kitchens2>
        <Kitchens2Objective>Using Kitchen Overview, build each missing object for making pizzas for the pizza joint kiosk.</Kitchens2Objective>
        <Kitchens3>Storage shelves and refrigerators need refilling by workmen just like drink despensers and drink kiosks. Once they have been stocked, chefs can take ingredients from them and begin the cooking process.</Kitchens3>
        <ChefsTitle>Chefs</ChefsTitle>
        <Chefs>Chefs need to be hired to cook the food and deliver it to the kiosks and displays. You can use the staff deployment screen, as explained in the Scheduling Workers Tutorial, to assign more than one chef. Simply click on the kitchen zone.</Chefs>
        <ChefsObjective>Hire and then assign at least 3 chefs to the kitchen.</ChefsObjective>
        <FinishedKitchenTitle>Finished Kitchen</FinishedKitchenTitle>
        <FinishedKitchen>Feel free to go back to the kitchen overview and use it to add more food types. You will then be able to serve more passengers at different kiosks and displays.</FinishedKitchen>
        <StoresTitle>Retail Stores</StoresTitle>
        <Stores>Although we have satisfied hunger and thirst, passengers can still get bored!
        
There are various simple stands and electronic services you can build to entertain pax. But, you can make a much greater profit with stores!</Stores>
        <BuildingStores>Each store requires a zone. They require a cash register to serve paying customers.</BuildingStores>
        <BuildingStoresObjective>Zone a new functioning store area.</BuildingStoresObjective>
        <ProductsTitle>Retail Products</ProductsTitle>
        <Products>There are various products that can be sold at various product displays, which you can get a list of inside of the Retail subcategory of the Build menu.
        
Each product has it's own popularity and profit level; hover over the options to see!</Products>
        <ProductStats>The profit level is the cost subtracted from revenue of each, while the popularity is the chance that someone may purchase it when browsing.
        
A passenger will visit a product display, and if they are impressed with what they see they will buy it. Else, they will move onto another display for a new chance to select.</ProductStats>
        <Boredom>Each time a passenger browses a display, they become less bored and even slightly less frustrated due to the calming nature of browsing.
        
There is no limit to how many times they can browse or even a limit on how much they can spend!</Boredom>
        <CustomizingTitle>Customizing Stores</CustomizingTitle>
        <Customizing>Feel free to sell one product type per store or to sell many products, it is up to you!
        
You can also customize the store names (and cafe names too) by clicking on them and selecting Rename!</Customizing>
        <StoresFinaleTitle>Finished Tutorial</StoresFinaleTitle>
        <StoresFinale>You can now deal with hunger, thirst, and boredom in your airports with cafes, kiosks, vending machines, and stores.
        
You did it all to make more money... I mean, it's all to make passengers happier.</StoresFinale>
    </FoodStores>
    <Default>Helpful images will appear here throughout the tutorial.</Default>
    <NeedsNegotiate>
        <IntroductionTitle>Airline Needs and Negotiation Tutorial</IntroductionTitle>
        <Introduction>Welcome to the Airline Needs and Negotiation tutorial!
        
So far you've got a successful airport, with many happy passengers and lots of money rolling in. But how do you make your airlines happier, and squeeze more money out of them?

Note: This tutorial is quite advanced, and most of what applies is only for medium and large airports.</Introduction>
        <AirlinesTitle>Why is airline satisfaction important?</AirlinesTitle>
        <Airlines>Airlines offer you flight schemas that you can assign to your gates within certain restricted times and gate sizes.
        
The more an airline is happy with your airport, the more flights they will offer you that you can earn revenue from. As long as you keep their other Needs met, you will be able to charge them higher prices. And you like money, don't you?</Airlines>
        <DifferentNeedsTitle>Different Airline Needs</DifferentNeedsTitle>
        <DifferentNeeds>
            <b>Trust</b>
        </DifferentNeeds>
        <MoreNeeds>Commercial Fees will stay good with a reasonable commercial price, which includes runway and terminal fees. Of course, you may want to sacrifice this rating in order to boost profits.
        
Some airlines care about Fuel Price and Fuel Failures. Those that do will expect good access to fuel with not too many turn downs, and/or at reasonable prices.</MoreNeeds>
        <FurtherNeeds>Some also care about Passenger Satisfaction. Quite simply the higher your passengers are satisfied, the greater this rating will be.
        
Service Reliability is about the overall passenger flight service, and is affected by how many passengers missed their flights, how many flights have been delayed, and how many were cancelled!</FurtherNeeds>
        <NegotiatedFacilities>This final need, Negotiated Facilities, is essencially a timer. It works out how long ago you negotiated away some facilities to the airline, and will continue to get worse until you assign what you promised them!
        
Later we will cover negotiations.</NegotiatedFacilities>
        <AirlineRepsTitle>Administrators and Sales Reps</AirlineRepsTitle>
        <AirlineReps>While not working on research, your administrators can </AirlineReps>
        <AirlineRepsObjective>Go to Airline Details view for Learnyville Air, click Select Rep, and then click Assign for them to represent the airline.</AirlineRepsObjective>
        <AirlineExecutivesTitle>Airline Executives</AirlineExecutivesTitle>
        <AirlineExecutives>Airline Executives are visitors who will come from the airlines to have meetings with the airline's reps. They cannot access areas blocked by staff doors.
        
Their satisfaction will affect the overall passenger satisfaction score, like regular passengers. Make sure the areas they stay in are decorated, and that they have access to food, drinks, toilets, and entertainment during breaks.</AirlineExecutives>
        <Reception>All visitors must first visit a Reception desk. Only Airline visitors can pass it, so use reception zones to create borders where you want regular passengers to stop.
        
As you can see, an area has been highlighted in the entrance of the business center. This would be a good place for security to stop passengers going further!</Reception>
        <ReceptionObjective>Add a functional Visitors Reception zone to the business center. The highlighted area is recommended.</ReceptionObjective>
        <OfficesPeek>Remember you'll normally need to hire an extra security guard to work there. This tutorial already gives you one extra.
        
You should be able see some empty offices in the north business center. We will get to these later! Notice that each Sales Rep works in their own office in the same way that the Administrators do.</OfficesPeek>
        <MoreReps>Having more than one rep can speed up the rate emails boost communication.
        
There is a limit to this effect, and you'll need to have meetings in order to reach the best communication levels. They take place around midday in a conference room, and are automatically scheduled by reps.</MoreReps>
        <MoreRepsObjective>Zone and build a functioning Conference Room. Ideally this should be in the north business area.</MoreRepsObjective>
        <CommercialPricingTitle>Commercial Pricing</CommercialPricingTitle>
        <CommercialPricing>You can set the costs of runway and terminal fees in the Operations screen. This will impact the Fees need of the airline, with each airline having their own sensitivity to it.
        
An alternative to this is negotiations. Negotiations allow us to push for higher prices. We trade facilities and other promises in return.</CommercialPricing>
        <RequirementsTitle>Negotiation Requirements</RequirementsTitle>
        <Requirements>Negotiated deals are... a big deal! Airlines will require a good prior history with them before you can negotiate with them.
        
You can hover over the Negotiate button to find out what is missing. You'll need to accept some flights at least.</Requirements>
        <RequirementsObjective>Go to Learnyville Air's detail viewer, fix the requirements, and then begin the negotiations.</RequirementsObjective>
        <NegotiationsTitle>Negotiations</NegotiationsTitle>
        <Negotiations>Because of what we trade back, you can charge airlines higher prices than normal without a hit to their satisfaction. However, you do need to make a good deal first!
        
In this screen, you can add additional planes and select a time slot for those planes to land in. This is useful if you need flights of a certain gate size or time slot.</Negotiations>
        <NegotiationsObjective>Click Call to begin!</NegotiationsObjective>
        <Wants>This is it! Now we are in round 1 of the negotiations. At the top you can see the current atmosphere score, which will become hot when there's a good deal and cold when the airline is less interested.
        
Below you can see what the airline wants for a variety of issues. Next to each want is the option to counter offer, by typing in a value or using the slider. You can make up to one non-negotiable if you really need a counter offer to stick.</Wants>
        <PricingTitle>Different Pricing Schemes</PricingTitle>
        <Pricing>There are four options for adjusting prices.
        
The breach penalty is simple: breach this contract and you'll pay this price!

In the side panel to the right, there is a tab called Terms, which covers what will breach the contract.</Pricing>
        <Pricing2>Terminal fees and runway fees replace the cost set in commercial prices.
        
Finally, there is the daily fee. This can be used as a supplementary cost to cover admin fees. For example, Sales Reps cost about $3000 a day to hire! With very large airlines, they may find it better to pay a single large daily fee rather than pay per flight and per passenger.</Pricing2>
        <AtmosphereTitle>Atmosphere</AtmosphereTitle>
        <Atmosphere>Let's experiment. First try to cool down the atmosphere! This will generally happen when you remove facilities and raise prices.</Atmosphere>
        <AtmosphereObjective>Make the deal worse to score a low atmosphere.</AtmosphereObjective>
        <HotDeal>Now let's heat things up! This time improve the deal by adding facilities and reducing prices.
        
Notice that for some facilities, above a point there is no effect on the score. Some airlines care less about certain facilities, and why would they want loads of what they don't like?</HotDeal>
        <HotDealObjective>Make the atmosphere hotter!</HotDealObjective>
        <BestDeal>On the right of the screen is three tabs, and a contextual pop up. When you are working on a specific issue, you can see more details about it. When you are not hovered over any issue, you can see a summary of the current deal, view the potential breach terms and conditions, and get some additional help.
        
We need to work on getting the best deal possible, but how do we do that?</BestDeal>
        <BestAtmosphere>You could simply let the atmosphere enter the Good or Hot area, and then accept the deal. However, while that might strike you a quick deal, it certainly won't earn you the best deal!
        
Airlines will sometimes hide their true feelings about a deal, and try not to reveal how much they are truly willing to sacrifice. To really figure out the best atmosphere will require the confidence to push the airline down, using experimentation and patience.</BestAtmosphere>
        <SendOfferTitle>Finishing Round 1</SendOfferTitle>
        <SendOffer>Once you have found a good set of deals to compromise on, click Send Offer. They will get back to you once they have discussed it amongst themselves.</SendOffer>
        <SendOfferObjective>Send them your counter offer!</SendOfferObjective>
        <OutcomesTitle>Three Outcomes</OutcomesTitle>
        <Outcomes>Let time pass and you will recieve one of these responses:
        
1) The airline accepted your offer.
        
2) The airline declined your offer.

3) The airline wanted to negotiate further, and you are now onto the next stage of negotiating.</Outcomes>
        <Overview>If they outright rejected your offer, it means that you set conditions so extreme that they could not work out a better deal from it!
            
Whichever way it went, let's assume they want to rengoatiate. You will see an overview screen, as shown in the image pop-out. This will compare their new counter offers to yours, and will help you determine how the deal is going. You would then continue onto Round 2, and continue the negotiation process as normal until it is over.</Overview>
        <EndingTitle>After Negotiations</EndingTitle>
        <Ending>Once finished, the airline will start demanding that you give them their facilities. You'll need to build or zone new facilities if you do not have any!
        
In the Airline Details view at the bottom, you can see the current deal and what is missing. In the Airline Needs section, you'll see the Facilities need. This will get worse the longer you take to give them their facilities!</Ending>
        <Assigning>To assign them facilities, click on it and select Assign Airline Exclusivity. Only airlines that are missing facilities will be listed here.
        
Be careful with gates! Only that airline's planes can land at them! Check the flight scheduler if any planes can no longer use that gate - they will turn red.</Assigning>
        <AssigningObjective>Assign all missing facilities. Use the Airline Details viewer to check what is missing.</AssigningObjective>
        <RoomScores>You should see a new need called Facility Quality. Each zone has a zone evaluation associated with it, and when you assign a zone to an airline they will take into account how good the zone is.
        
You can click on a negotiable zone to see it's overall score and score breakdowns. It includes the environment, zone size, ease of access, and more!</RoomScores>
        <OfficesTitle>Offices</OfficesTitle>
        <Offices>You may have given them offices. These will be used by Airline Executives who work during the morning and afternoon. They too have needs, like the conference room users, and will try to sort them out during breaks.
        
As such, they will impact your overall satisfaction if they are unhappy! This is where a large business center with many facilities is necessary. Remember, you can profit off of them using certain facilities!</Offices>
        <FinishedTitle>That's it!</FinishedTitle>
        <Finished>You have learned more about airline needs, interest, sales reps, conference rooms, negotiations, and negotiated facilities!</Finished>
    </NeedsNegotiate>
</Tutorial>
